BOB DYLAN
State Theatre, Sydney, Australia
April 15, 1992 (incomplete soundboard recording)

A rare Soundboard recording from 1992.  Thanks to oootttiiisss for his request.

Lineage: Trade cdr from the UK > EAC (no errors) > hdd > frequency and spectral analysis [not
lossy] > flac > torrent > Dime

One Disc — 60:27

1.  Delia [first since May 1960 in Minneapolis]
2.  Union Sundown
3.  Just Like A Woman
4.  Stuck Inside of Mobile with the Memphis Blues Again
5.  I'll Be Your Baby Tonight
6.  If Not For You [second ever, first was night before]
7.  Love Minus Zero/No Limit
8.  Little Moses
9.  It's All Over Now, Baby Blue
10. A Hard Rain's A-Gonna’ Fall
11. Cat's in the Well
12. Idiot Wind (cut)


Complete show is 18 songs over 95 minutes.

1.  Rainy Day Women [not included]
2 — 13.  THIS RECORDING
14. The Times They Are A-Changin' [not included]
15. Highway 61 Revisited [not included]
16. Absolutely Sweet Marie [not included]
17. Ballad Of A Thin Man [not included]
18. Blowin' In The Wind [not included]

Enjoy!  Thanks to shinsuke and jantemp for all these '92s.  I’ll seed this at least until I leave tomorrow night to go see Bob at State College,
Pennsylvania.  :-))
