BOB DYLAN
Royal Lahanina Tennis Stadium
Maui, Hawaii
April 22, 1992

Lineage: Trade CDRs > EAC (no errors) > hdd > frequency & spectral analysis (not lossy) > flac
via TLH level 8 w/ checksums

Excellent sound.  Nice performance too, after a few days off.

Disc One – 14 tracks, 69:59
1.  Introduction & Rainy Day Women # 12 & 35
2.  Lay Lady Lay
3.  Union Sundown
4.  Just Like A Woman
5.  Tangled Up In Blue
6.  I'll Be Your Baby Tonight
7.  She Belongs To Me
8.  Love Minus Zero/No Limit
9.  Little Moses
10. Visions Of Johanna
11. Don't Think Twice, It's All Right
12. Cat's In The Well
13. Idiot Wind
14. The Times They Are A-Changin' [with fade-out into opening notes of Maggie’s Farm]

Disc Two – 4 tracks, 20:47

15. Maggie's Farm [with fade-in from crowd at end of Times]
—
16. Absolutely Sweet Marie
17. All Along The Watchtower
18. Blowin' In The Wind


In thanks to shinsuke for his Spring ‘92 torrents.

Artwork at Ole’s site, but for a different disc split:
http://www.dylanimages.com/Mauimaui_220492.Jpg 