BOB DYLAN
Kearnes Center, Univ. of Missouri
Columbia, Missouri
April 24, 2001

last ever Highlands

Lineage:  trade cdrs from excellent USA source > EAC (no errors) > spectrum check (not lossy,
not much over 17K) > flac > torrent

Excellent sound; may be same source recording as LB-3331, but not same version, did not
observe issues identified with that one.  “A” or “A-“ quality.  I really like this tour and this show
— hope you do too!

Disc 1 – 74:00

1.  Roving Gambler
2.  Mr. Tambourine Man
3.  Desolation Row
4.  Everything Is Broken
5.  Make You Feel My Love
6.  Stuck Inside Of Mobile With The Memphis Blues Again
7.  Masters Of War
8.  Girl From The North Country
9.  Tangled Up In Blue
10.  Highlands
11.  The Wicked Messenger

Disc 2 – 46:56

1.  Leopard-Skin Pill-Box Hat
—encore— [clapping cut]
2.  Things Have Changed
3.  Like A Rolling Stone
4.  If Dogs Run Free
5.  All Along The Watchtower
6.  Knockin' On Heaven's Door
7.  Highway 61 Revisited
8.  Blowin' In The Wind 

