Bob Dylan
Orpheum Theater
Omaha, Nebraska
April 1, 2025


A fine Rough and Rowdy Bob Dylan show from the new tour. A great band and a nice recording.  Sample below.


24bit 48K recording. If you still burn to CD, it's pretty easy to convert the files to CD specs. Most burning programs do it internally. If burning, divide discs before Desolation Row.


CMC-8 mics>>Sony PCM-A10>>ProTools (for level adjustment, eq, compression, and song separation)>Flac

Taped by gravenb. Mastered by JB. Please don't sell. Please do not convert to lossy format and upload anywhere. 


(1:48:15)

01 I'll Be Your Baby Tonight
02 It Ain't Me, Babe
03 I Contain Multitudes
04 False Prophet
05 When I Paint My Masterpiece
06 Black Rider
07 My Own Version Of You
08 To Be Alone With You
09 Crossing The Rubicon
10 Desolation Row 
11 Key West (Philosopher Pirate)
12 Watching The River Flow
13 It's All Over Now, Baby Blue
14 I've Made Up My Mind To Give Myself To You
15 Mother Of Muses
16 Goodbye Jimmy Reed
17 Every Grain Of Sand