July 2, 1988
Great Woods Performing Arts Center
Mansfield, Massachusetts

“Pay For Your Ticket And Don’t Complain,” by Southside Butcher


101.  Subterranean Homesick Blues
102.  Pretty Peggy-O
103.  Had A Dream About You, Baby
104.  Ballad Of A Thin Man
105.  Stuck Inside Of Mobile With The Memphis Blues Again
106.  Tangled Up In Blue
107.  Mr. Tambourine Man

201.  Love Minus Zero - No Limit
202.  It Ain't Me, Babe
203.  I Shall Be Released
204.  Silvio
205.  All Along The Watchtower
206.  The Times They Are A- Changin'
207.  Maggie's Farm
208.  Like A Rolling Stone

Live debut of Pretty Peggy-O; second ever (of four) Had A Dream About You Baby

Artwork is available at Ole’s site.