BOB DYLAN
Worcester Memorial Auditorium
Worcester, Massachusetts
December 8, 1995


Lineage:  trade CDRS > eac > hdd > frequency & spectral check (no lossy signs detected) > flac
(no sector boundary issues) > torrent


Disc One
1. Crash On The Levee (Down In The Flood)
2. I Want You
3. All Along The Watchtower
4. Simple Twist Of Fate
5. Most Likely You Go Your Way (And I'll Go Mine)
6. Silvio
7. Mr. Tambourine Man
8. Masters Of War

Disc Two
1. Love Minus Zero/No Limit
2. God Knows
3. I and I
4. Highway 61 Revisited (audience /encore clapping cut by taper)
---
5. Alabama Getaway
6. Girl Of The North Country
---
7. Rainy Day Women #12 & 35


Fingerprints:
1) beginning of D1T2 — “how ya’ doin’ Bob”
2) transition between D1T3 and T4 — “Alright JJ, way to smoke buddy”
3) My Favorite:  D1T7 at 7:04 — after obnoxious yelling during Tambourine Man, person next
to taper goes “shhhhhh” (but it doesn’t work to stop drunks in right channel)
4) D2T1 5:56 — hostility from taper’s neighbors to the yahoos: “get these people out of here”
5) band intros at end of D2T3 and over transition to T4

Excellent high energy show from the “Lost Paradise” Tour, played in the old 1930s vintage, now
endangered Worcester Memorial Auditorium, about 100 km from where I grew up.  Gopherstick
says: “Sound:  8.5 (crystal clear vocals, the drums are buried under the guitars and bass.  The
sound drops a bit after the acoustic set, hence the sound grade).  Highlights: I Want You, Simple
Twist of Fate, I & I Comments: Bob's vocals are a little worn around the corners here but he's
singing with confidence and conviction. The I & I tonight is an amazing venting session by Bob.
He starts off screaming, then gets worse. By the end he moaning out lines in a high pitched wail
that'll raise the neck hairs.  Bottom Line: High energy show, track this one down and enjoy.”