Bob Dylan and His Band 2009-Aug-05 Corpus Christi, Texas ***24-bit/48kHz ***

Bob Dylan and His Band 
Corpus Christi, Texas
Whataburger Field
2009-Aug-05

taper: ballpark center field, approx. 30 yards from the stage right speaker stack 
Edirol R-09HR (internal mics ) > 24-bit/48 kHz WAV > SDcard > HDD > Cool Edit (tracks only) > flac level 8 (TLH) 

at the request of the taper, one small edit was made
to remove about 50 sec of crowd chatter during the encore break 
near the end of track 11.  
There were no other edits or processing.

NOTE: this torrent consists of 24-bit/48kHz stereo WAV files 
that are not burnable by the red-book CD Audio standard.


00 intro
01 Watching The River Flow (Bob on guitar, Donnie on pedal steel)
02 Don't Think Twice, It's All Right ((Bob on guitar, Donnie on lap steel, Stu on acoustic guitar, Tony on standup bass)
03 'Til I Fell In Love With You (Bob on keyboard then harp center stage, Donnie on lap steel)
04 Spirit On The Water (Bob on keyboard and harp, Donnie on pedal steel, Tony on standup bass) 
05 Rollin' And Tumblin' (Bob on keyboard, Donnie on electric mandolin, Denny on slide guitar, Stu on acoustic guitar)
06 Workingman's Blues #2 (Bob on keyboard, Donnie on pedal steel, Stu on acoustic guitar)
07 Tweedle Dee & Tweedle Dum (Bob on keyboard, Donnie on pedal steel)) 
08 Ballad Of A Thin Man (Bob on keyboard and harp, Donnie on lap steel)
09 Highway 61 Revisited (Bob on keyboard, Donnie on lap steel) 
10 Nettie Moore (Bob on keyboard and harp, Donnie on viola, Stu on acoustic guitar) 
11 Thunder On The Mountain (Bob on keyboard, Donnie on lap steel, Stu on acoustic guitar)
(encore) 
12 Like A Rolling Stone (Bob on keyboard, Donnie on lap steel) 
13 Jolene (Bob on keyboard, Donnie on lap steel, Tony on standup bass) 
14 All Along The Watchtower (Bob on keyboard, Donnie on lap steel) 

Band Members 
Bob Dylan - keyboard, guitar, harp 
Tony Garnier - bass 
George Recile - drums 
Stu Kimball - rhythm guitar 
Denny Freeman - lead guitar 
Donnie Herron - viola, electric mandolin, pedal steel, lap steel 