BOB DYLAN
Bell Auditorium
Augusta, Georgia
October 10, 1995

Lineage:  shn files on trade CDRs from a certain Dylanomaniac in the north country > hdd > md5
verify ( > convert one file on each disc for spectral analysis, no lossy indicia) > torrent > Dime

Artwork by Carine of Paris included.

Disc One — 66:42
1. Drifter's Escape
2. Tonight I'll Be Staying Here With You
3. All Along the Watchtower
4. Simple Twist of Fate
5. It Takes A Lot To Laugh, It Takes A Trian to Cry
6. Silvio
7. Mr. Tambourine Man
8. Masters of War
9. Don't Think Twice, It's All Right

Disc Two — 46:52
1. crowd noise
2. God Knows
3. I'll Remember You
4. Band Intros
5. Obviously Five Beleivers
6. Alabama Getaway
7. It Ain't Me, Babe
8. Rainy Day Women #12 & 35


Gopherstick says:  Sound: 9 (the crowd is below you if that makes any sense, the vocals are nice
and clear.  The guitars are up but Bob's is loudest, which is never a good thing.  Otherwise
excellent balance).  Highlights: a ragged but glorious Don't Think Twice, It's All Right. 
Comments: The crowd is partying down, cheering and screaming the night away.  This recording
really throws you in the middle of the venue surrounded on all sides by packs of happy fans.  And
hey, Bob seems to have finally figured out how he wants to sing on the faster song: just barrel
through and have a good raw time.  Bottom Line: High energy tonight, you can't go wrong
trading for this one.”