December 14, 1995
Beacon Theatre
New York, NY

Lineage:  flac > DVD > hdd > wav > Trade CDRs > EAC (no errors) > hdd > FA & SA check
(not lossy, full range) > flac (level 8, align of sector boundaries) > torrent

I have two recordings of this show.  For this one, the fingerprint is a discussion at D2T2, at 7:52 -
8:08 about a place on “55th Street” and “keyboard player” named “Jerry Lee Lewis.”  Some
slightly irritating noise in a few places as if from the mic being touched or moved by the taper. 
This mainly occurs during d1t06 (several times) and on one or two other tracks.  There is also a
slight dropout flaw on d2t5.


Excellent sound.  Huge performance, very energetic crowd.  One of the best NET “Tom Thumb’s
Blues” I’ve heard.  Artwork from Great North Woods included.

Disc One — 70:04
1.  Drifter's Escape
2.  Tonight I'll Be Staying Here With You 
3.  All Along The Watchtower
4.  Simple Twist Of Fate
5.  Just Like Tom Thumb's Blues 
6.  Silvio 
7.  Tangled Up In Blue
8.  Masters Of War
9.  Mama, You Been On My Mind
10.  Dark Eyes (w/ Patti Smith on vocals)

Disc Two — 43:24
1.  Joey
2.  Highway 61 Revisited
----
3.  Alabama Getaway 
4.  One Too Many Mornings
5.  Rainy Day Women # 12 & 35 (w/ G.E. Smith on guitar)


Gopherstick loves this show, and the ‘stick knows his Bob:
“Sound: 9 (exceptional quality, vocals are loud, clear and upfront, and the band sounds crisp and
separated).  Highlights: Just Like Tom Thumb's Blues, Dark Eyes, Joey, One Too Many
Mornings.  Comments: The crowd is ready to explode and Bob is the flame over the gasoline. 
But enough with that shit, I'm guessing the bootleggers passed this one up due to the standard
setlist.  Bob shows them what they know, this is my favorite One Too Many Mornings of the
year, and the duet with Patti Smith is a knockout as usual.  Bottom Line: A stunning concert, one
of the best of the month, if not the year.” 