Richmond Mosque
Richmond, Virginia
October 21, 1990

First NET show after the departure of G.E. Smith at the completion of the five-night stand at the
New York Beacon on October 19, 1990.  John Staehely and Cesar Diaz on guitars, Tony Garnier
on bass, and Christopher Parker on drums.

Lineage:  trade cdrs > eac > flac

Disc One
1. Dixie (Daniel Decatur Emmett)
2. Subterranean Homesick Blues
3. I'll Remember You
4. Ballad Of A Thin Man
5. Gotta Serve Somebody						
6. Masters Of War
7. Joey
8. Don't Think Twice, It's All Right
9. Gates Of Eden
10. Desolation Row

Disc Two 
11. It Ain't Me, Babe
12. Wiggle Wiggle
13. Shooting Star
14. All Along The Watchtower
15. I Believe In You
16. Like A Rolling Stone
—
17. The Times They Are A-Changin'
18. Highway 61 Revisited
