BOB DYLAN
“A Wanderer By Trade” by Southside Butcher
Fiddler’s Green Amphitheatre
Denver, Colorado
June 15, 1988

Lineage: a friend in Germany’s hard drive (original June 2004 files) > dvd data disc > my hard
drive > hungercity

CD 1

1.  Subterranean Homesick Blues
2.  One More Cup Of Coffee (Valley Below)
3.  It's All Over Now, Baby Blue
4.  Stuck Inside Of Mobile With The Memphis Blues Again
5.  You're A Big Girl Now
6.  Ballad Of A Thin Man
7.  Mama, You Been On My Mind
8.  Eileen Aroon
9.  Don't Think Twice, It's All Right
10. Just Like A Woman 


CD 2

1.  Seeing The Real You At Last
2.  Simple Twist Of Fate
3.  Like A Rolling Stone
4.  A Hard Rain's A-Gonna Fall
5.  Maggie's Farm

Bonus Tracks:
6.  Tangled Up In Blue (East Troy, WI, June 18, 1988)
7.  It Ain’t Me Babe (East Troy, WI, June 18, 1988)
8.  Gotta Serve Somebody (East Troy, WI, June 18, 1988)
9.  Tomorrow Is A Long Time (Saratoga Springs, NY, June 26, 1988)
10. Shelter From The Storm (Saratoga Springs, NY, June 26, 1988)


