BOB DYLAN
Roskilde Rock Festival
Dyrskuepladsen
Roskilde, Denmark
June 29, 1990

Trade discs > EAC > flac level 6
Excellent sound, Bob’s right out front.

Disc One – 48:24
1.  Absolutely Sweet Marie
2.  Ballad Of A Thin Man
3.  Stuck Inside Of Mobile With The Memphis Blues Again
4.  Queen Jane Approximately
5.  Masters Of War
6.  Gotta Serve Somebody
7.  It's Alright, Ma (I'm Only Bleeding)
8.  It's All Over Now, Baby Blue
9.  One Too Many Mornings

Disc Two – 46:50
1.  Don't Think Twice, It's All Right
2.  Mr. Tambourine Man
3.  Leopard-Skin Pill-Box Hat
4.  Political World
5.  Shooting Star
6.  All Along The Watchtower
7.  I Shall Be Released
8.  Like A Rolling Stone
—
9.  Blowin' In The Wind
10. Highway 61 Revisited
