BOB DYLAN
Marjorie Merriweather Post Pavilion
Columbia, Maryland
July 29, 2000

In honor of Bob’s fifth show at Merriweather Post in Columbia, Maryland, coming up only three
weeks away now, here’s Bob’s last show (fourth overall, after June 1981, July 1988, and July
1989) at that venue.  The only listed LB (LB-4002), which I don’t have; therefore, I cannot
compare to say whether this is the same recording.  LB-4002, however, is an MD recording, and
this one appears to be full spectrum.  Excellent sound, A-.

Lineage:  Trade CDRs (year 2004) > EAC (no errors) > FA & SA (full spectrum, does not appear
to be MD) > Wavtrim > rename files to protocol > flac (level 8, align on sector boundaries) >
torrent.

Scouser artwork included matches track and disc splits for this recording.

Disc One – 68:23
1.  Duncan And Brady
2.  To Ramona
3.  Desolation Row
4.  It's All Over Now, Baby Blue
5.  Tangled Up In Blue
6.  Searching For A Soldier's Grave
7.  Watching The River Flow
8.  Every Grain Of Sand
9.  Maggie's Farm
10.  Dignity
11.  Cold Irons Bound
12.  Band Introductions

Disc Two
1.  Leopard-Skin Pill-Box Hat
— > (encore)
2.  Things Have Changed
3.  Like A Rolling Stone
4.  It Ain't Me, Babe
5.  Highway 61 Revisited
6.  Blowin' In The Wind 
