BOB DYLAN
Northwest Georgia Trade & Convention Center
Dalton, Georgia
Weds., May 2, 2001


Lineage:  Trade CDRs > EAC > FA and Spectrum check (not lossy, not much over 17K) >
FLAC level 6 (align on sector boundaries)

Different than LB-5072, though may or may not be same recording.  Sound volume changes (up)
at about 2:03 of D1T1, perhaps too high.  Pop at D1T1-2:39.  Very good sound, B+ or A-


Disc One – 65:19
1.  Duncan And Brady
2.  My Back Pages
3.  Desolation Row
4.  Down In The Flood
5.  Tell Me That It Isn't True
6.  Stuck Inside Of Mobile With The Memphis Blues Again
7.  Mama, You Been On My Mind
8.  Fourth Time Around
9.  Tangled Up In Blue
10. Searching For A Soldier's Grave
11. Standing In The Doorway

Disc Two – 63:15
1.  Cold Irons Bound
2.  Leopard-Skin Pill-Box Hat
— 1st encore
3.  Things Have Changed
4.  Like A Rolling Stone
5.  If Dogs Run Free
6.  All Along The Watchtower
7.  Knockin' On Heaven's Door
8.  Highway 61 Revisited
9.  Blowin' In The Wind
— 2nd encore
10. Rainy Day Women #12 & 35