Festival Hall, Tampa Bay Performing Arts Center
Tampa, Florida
November 14, 1989

CDR trade discs, received in trade as “Can’t Buy a Thrill,” Southside Butcher productions.

Lineage:  Trade CDRs > EAC > Audacity for various glitch fixes; almost all track markers reset
> flac (level 8, align on sector boundaries) > torrent

Does not match LB-2173; I do not have that LB entry and so cannot determine whether this
recording or the alternate recording discussed below is the same as the LB-2173 recording.

The largest problem with this recording is on D1T1 (Stuck Inside of Mobile), which is clipped by
8 or 10 seconds, comes in on the “up and down the block” line of Stuck Inside of Mobile.

I have a second copy of this show (D1/7T-38:59 + D2/10T-63:43).  That second version also
does not match LB-2173 by disc splits or times, but does have the beginning of Stuck Inside of
Mobile.  The sound on that second recording is inferior to this recording (though it improves on
the acoustic set at the beginning of D2).   That second recording is different than this one, as it
does not have the "Roger McGuinn" fingerprint on KOHD that this recording has.  I have tried to
patch the beginning of Stuck Inside of Mobile from that second recording into this recording.  I
am torrenting TWO versions of D1T1 – one clipped as received and one “patched.”  Obviously,
burn the show with only one of those versions of Stuck Inside, as you like.


Disc One — 48:57

1.  Stuck Inside Of Mobile With The Memphis Blues Again (5:59)
1A.  Stuck Inside Of Mobile [patched/spliced, optional] (6:06)
2.  I Want You (4:27)
3.  Ballad Of A Thin Man (8:43)
4.  Man Of Peace (5:21)
5.  Simple Twist Of Fate (6:29)
6.  I Believe In You (6:10)
7.  Rainy Day Women # 12 & 35 (4:12)
	[4:00-04 glitches/intermittencies in crowd noise between songs, not repairable]
8.  It's All Over Now, Baby Blue (7:36) [fades out]

Disc Two — 60:02
1.  It Ain't Me, Babe (8:39) [fades in]
2.  Mr. Tambourine Man (8:00)
3.  Everything Is Broken (4:06)
4 . What Good Am I? (5:17)
5.  Most Of The Time (6:32)
6.  It Takes A Lot To Laugh, It Takes A Train To Cry (6:04)
	[levels increase momentarily in crowd noise at 6:02.3;
	minor drop at 6:04.4; track marker placed there]
7.  Like A Rolling Stone (7:14) [encore clapping fades out]
---
8.  Knockin' On Heaven's Door (6:47) [fades in] [“Roger McGuinn” fingerprint at 0:44.5]
9.  Maggie's Farm (7:23)

some clipping on crowd nearby taper between songs
some bass hum/hiss in some locations

Fingerprint:  At 0:44.5 of KOHD a man in left channel distinctly says "Roger McGuinn" while
two other voices nearby are making same observation not as loudly.

Well above average sound for a US late 89; does not match LB-2173.

Roger McGuinn on guitar for encores.

Interesting show -- the songs tend to run together, one right into the next (which makes setting
the track markers a challenge!).  This early Oh Mercy! show features back to back Everything is
Broken, an excellent What Good Am I?, and a sublime Most of the Time, maybe the best.