Bob Dylan
Brooklyn Bowl
Nashville, TN
March 26, 2024


Gravenb gets a fantastic recording at the tiny Brooklyn Bowl in Nashville. First of two nights.  Samples below.

24bit 48K recording. If you still burn to CD, it's pretty easy to convert the files to CD specs. Most burning programs do it internally. If burning, divide discs before Key West.

CA-11 mics>CA Battery Box>Edirol R-09HR>>ProTools (for level adjustment, eq, compression, RX, and song separation)>Flac

Taped by gravenb. Mastered by JB. Please don't sell. Please do not convert to lossy format and upload anywhere. 



(1:47:39)

01. Watching The River Flow  
02. Most Likely You Go Your Way (And I'll Go Mine) 
03. I Contain Multitudes 
04. False Prophet 
05. When I Paint My Masterpiece 
06. Black Rider
07. I'll Be Your Baby Tonight
08. My Own Version Of You 
09. Crossing the Rubicon
10. To Be Alone With You 
11. Key West (Philosopher Pirate) 
12. Gotta Serve Somebody 
13. I've Made Up My Mind To Give Myself To You 
14. Big River 
15. Mother Of Muses 
16. Goodbye Jimmy Reed 
17. Every Grain Of Sand
