BOB DYLAN
San Luis Obispo, California
March 11, 2000


Lineage:  trade cdrs > EAC (no errors) > spectrum & frequency check (not lossy) > FLAC (level
6) > torrent

LB lists two versions, one a Soomlos and one unidentified (LB-3685).  Both are graded B+.  This
is not the Soomlos, and may or may not be the same recording as the LB-3685 but does not
match the disc splits or times of that one.  This one matches the disc splits on the Scouser
artwork, which is included (I’ve also included Carine’s artwork, which is generic).  Sound is very
good plus, a tiny bit distant, I’d give it an A-.

Disc One – 57:52.69

1.  I Am The Man Thomas
2.  Song To Woody
3.  It's Alright Ma (I’m Only Bleeding)
4.  Tangled Up In Blue
5.  This World Can't Stand Long
6.  Dignity
7.  Country Pie
8.  Tell Me That It Isn't True
9.  Things Have Changed
10. Not Dark Yet
11. Highway 61 Revisited

Disc Two – 33:59.16

— encore — 
1.  Love Sick
2.  Like A Rolling Stone
3.  It Ain't Me Babe
4.  Not Fade Away
5.  Blowin In The Wind 