BOB DYLAN
Merriweather Post Pavilion
Columbia, Maryland
June 14, 1981

In honor of Bob’s fifth appearance at Merriweather Post, Columbia, Maryland, coming up in two
weeks, and the start of a new tour tonight, I am torrenting a major upgrade (over either existing
LB version) of Bob’s first Merriweather Post appearance in the summer of 1981, with significant
Audacity cleanup as well.  Excellent sound for a 1981 AUD recording, especially on Disc 2, A-
quality.  Lots of great Bobtalk to: my favorite “I was country before it was cool.  I was a whole
lot of things before it was cool.”

4th show of the year 1981; 4th Shot Of Love Tour show

Disc One — 63:04

	Clydie King, Carolyn Dennis, Regina Havis, Madelyn Quebec, Willie Smith
1.  Come On In This House (3:26)
2.  It's Gonna Rain (4:16)
3.  Show Me The Way Lord (2:53)
4.  Saved By the Grace of Your Love (3:24)

5.  Gotta Serve Somebody (4:06)
6.  I Believe in You (5:17)
7.  Like A Rolling Stone (5:48)

	Regina McCreary
8.  Till I Get It Right (3:34)

9.  Man Gave Names To All the Animals (4:43)
10. Maggie’s Farm (3:43)
11. Simple Twist of Fate (4:15)
12. Ballad of a Thin Man (4:20)
13. Girl of the North Country (4:19)
14. Dead Man Dead Man (4:32)

	Carolyn Dennis
15. Walk Around Heaven All Day (4:28)


Disc Two — 58:37

1.  Abraham Martin & John (3:01)
2.  Lenny Bruce (5:24)
3.  Just Like Tom Thumb's Blues (4:24)
4.  We Just Disagree (2:27)
5.  Solid Rock (4:24)
6.  Watered Down Love (5:25)
7.  Just Like A Woman (4:14)
8.  Forever Young (4:13)
9.  When You Gonna Wake Up? (5:12)
10. In the Garden – > Band Intros (8:56)
— Encores
11. Blowin’ in the Wind (5:16)
12. Don’t Think Twice It’s All Right (5:38)


LINEAGE:  Trade CDRs > EAC > Audacity > flac level 8 (align on sector boundaries) >
maketorret

NOTES:  This is a complete recording of an excellent First Shot Of Love Tour show, including
all of the “girls’ songs.”  Fourth ever Dead Man, Dead Man, fourth ever Lenny Bruce, fourth ever
Watered Down Love.

There is no similar version on LB.  Neither LB has the girls’ songs.  LB-76 is also missing
Regina McCreary’s Till I Get It Right.

The recording has three flaws, and the CDRs I received had a few others.

The recording’s flaws: (1) the start of the first gospel singers’ song is clipped by a few seconds;
(2) the start of Simple Twist Of Fate is clipped by about four seconds, perhaps by a tape flip; and
(3) the transition between D2T6 and D2T7 is clipped, perhaps by a tape flip, but no music is
missing.  Both LB versions mention that there is a cut at D1T6 (though on LB-901 that points to
the wrong song).

The CDRs flaws have almost all been carefully fixed in Audacity.  LB-76 also notes the
problems in Watered Down Love and In The Garden, leading me to believe that this recording
and the LB-76 recording may have the same source.  LB-901 also notes the Watered Down Love
issue.
1.  D2T6 (Watered Down Love): (a) three second intermittency in right track at 4:25 fixed by
making those three seconds mono from the left track; (b) 0.25 second intermittency at 4:28, fixed
the same way; (c) very very minor intermittency in right channel at 4:35-37 not fixed. 
2.  D2T7 (Just Like A Woman): four loud clicks/pops removed/mitigated at 1:03.06, 1:31.57;
1:40.79; and 2:23.12.
3.  D2T10 (In The Garden): major drop-out in right channel at 4:44 to 5:22; dropped out /
became intermittent again at 5:47 during Band Intros, to end of track; both fixed by mono
substitutions from left channel.
4.  D2T11 (Blowin’ in the Wind): still very slight intermittency at 0:07.8 - 0:08.5, and at 5:04-
5:05 during cheering, decided not to repair give brevity.