Bob Dylan
Talking Stick Resort Amphitheatre 
Phoenix, AZ
May 13, 2025


First night of the 2025 incarnation of the the Outlaw Music Festival Tour. A great band and a great recording.  Very eclectic setlist. Very cool arrangements. First Mr. Tambourine Man in forever and a nice Pogues cover. Samples below.


24bit 48K recording. If you still burn to CD, it's pretty easy to convert the files to CD specs. Most burning programs do it internally.


CMC-8 mics>>Sony PCM-A10>>ProTools (for level adjustment, eq, compression, and song separation)>Flac

Taped by gravenb. Mastered by JB. Please don't sell. Please do not convert to lossy format and upload anywhere. 


(1:04:08)

01. I'll Be Your Baby Tonight
02. It Ain't Me, Babe
03. Forgetful Heart
04. Axe and the Wind (George “Wild Child” Butler cover)
05. To Ramona
06. Route 66 (Bobby Troup cover)
07. All Along the Watchtower
08. I'll Make It All Up To You (Charlie Rich cover)
09. It Takes a Lot to Laugh, It Takes a Train to Cry
10. Mr. Tambourine Man
11. Under the Red Sky
12. Scarlet Town
13. A Rainy Night in Soho (The Pogues cover)