Bob Dylan
Santa Barbara Bowl
Santa Barbara, CA
September 7, 2008

Great show at a small venue.  Taped from the 13th row slightly stage left.  Great sound.


Sonics>BatteryBox>Sony D7 DAT>ProTools (for level adjustment, compression, eq, and song separation)>flac

Taped and mastered by JB.  Please don't sell or convert to lossy format.


Disc 1  (61:13)

1. Cat's In The Well
2. The Times They Are A-Changin'
3. The Levee's Gonna Break
4. Don't Think Twice, It's All Right
5. Million Miles
6. Desolation Row
7. A Hard Rain's A-Gonna Fall
8. Honest With Me
9. I Believe In You

Disc 2 (53:28)

1. It's Alright, Ma (I'm Only Bleeding)
2. When The Deal Goes Down
3. Highway 61 Revisited 
4. Ain't Talkin'
5. Thunder On The Mountain
 	 
Encore 	
6. Like A Rolling Stone
7. Blowin' In The Wind
