BOB DYLAN
Santa Barbara County Bowl
Santa Barbara, California
May 20, 1995
NET Concert # 674

Lineage:  Trade CDRs > EAC (no errors) > hdd > FA & SA check (full spectrum, not lossy) >
flac level 8

Excellent sound.  The performance is considered, calm and focused, everything in its place. 
Another in a run of excellent May 1995 shows.

Artwork by Tynstra included, but disc splits are different.

Fingerprints:  D1T7 at 0:13, a female yells “Happy Birthday”; at D2T3 at 0:26, during band
introductions, a male yells “Hurricane!” right next to taper.

Disc One — 54:32
1. Crash On The Levee (Down In The Flood)
2. Senor (Tales Of Yankee Power)
3. All Along The Watchtower
4. Just Like A Woman
5. Silvio (Dylan/Hunter)
6. Watching The River Flow
7. Mr. Tambourine Man [tape flip at end]
8. Masters Of War
9. Love Minus Zero/No Limit [Bobtalk at 0:25 re Hoyt Axton; fadeout at 6:27, last 11 seconds
silent]

Disc Two — 43:04
10. Seeing The Real You At Last
11. Simple Twist Of Fate
12. It Takes A Lot To Laugh, It Takes A Train To Cry [2:50 crowd noise at end]
—
13. Like A Rolling Stone
14. My Back Pages



Gopherstick:  Sound: 8 (interesting sound to this tape. Vocals are way out in front and the whole
thing is a little compressed, but it sounds great nonetheless. The harmonica cuts through
everything and will knock the teeth out of your head if you're not ready for it. I like the feel of
this one a lot).  Highlights: Senor, Watching the River Flow, Love Minus Zero/No Limit. 
[Editorial comment by OutsideTLaw: sweet Simple Twist of Fate, too.]   Comments: Lets see if
Bob is in a good mood tonight.  After Crash on the Levee Bob deadpans, "Thank you.  We were
in LA last night and, uh, the OJ jury was there."  Good Mood :1, Bad Mood: 0.  Then he says
hello to his buddy Hoyt Axton, calls him "one of the best songwriters and singers of all times ...
and his Mom's not too shabby, either!  She wrote a song, can't remember what it is ... something
about a hotel."  Good Mood: 2, Bad Mood: 0.  Bottom Line: Fun show with an oddly addictive
sound and great Bob Talk. Pick this one up.