Lineage:  Trade CDRs > EAC (no errors) > frequency and spectrum check (full spectrum and
frequency, levels appear raised to 100%) > flac (level 6, align on sector boundaries) > torrent

Does not appear to have the cut/drop after Stone Walls / before Tangled Up In Blue noted by
Heinrich on his NTK HC torrent

Excellent sound, loud and clear; some clipping.

Disc One – 71:14

1.  Maggie's Farm
2.  Tonight I'll Be Staying Here With You
3.  Cold Irons Bound
4.  Tears Of Rage
5.  Can't Wait
6.  Silvio
7.  Stone Walls And Steel Bars
8.  Tangled Up In Blue
9.  Mr. Tambourine Man
10.  Friend Of The Devil
11. ́Til I Fell In Love With You

Disc Two – 33:56

1.  Highway 61 Revisited
---
2.  Like A Rolling Stone
3.  Forever Young
4.  Love Sick
5.  Rainy Day Women # 12 & 35