BOB DYLAN
The Charles Ives Center
Western Connecticut State College
Danbury, Connecticut
Saturday, May 11, 1991

17 Tracks - 67:35

Unknown Taper > Trade cdr (2004) > EAC (no errors) > FA & SA (no lossy generation, little
above 17K, TV band at 16K) > FLAC (level 6) > HC

Excellent sound, especially for 1991.  Bright clear and upfront, A-.

Appears to be same recording as LB-4048; has anomaly at T8-2:50 [not 2:54].  Don’t notice the
pops reported at T13.


1. Dixie (Daniel Decatur Emmett)
2. New Morning
3. Lay Lady Lay
4. All Along The Watchtower
5. Simple Twist Of Fate
6. Gotta Serve Somebody
7. Wiggle Wiggle
8. Bob Dylan's Dream
9. Don't Think Twice, It's All Right
10. Desolation Row
11. It Ain't Me, Babe
12. Everything Is Broken
13. Positively 4th Street
14. Rainy Day Women # 12 & 35
15. Man In The Long Black Coat
16. I Shall Be Released
17. Like A Rolling Stone

Last Dixie until Masked and Anonymous, July 2002.


Fingerprints:

1.  Talking beginning of T5; at around 0:30 taper(?) discussing the “tape”?
2.  Bobtalk:  T6/0:01 - 0:07:  “I wanna say hello to all of you Connecticut Yankees out there —
from one Connecticut Yankee to another”
3.  T8/0:19-0:22 – Guy:  “I don’t think you like this guy too much.”  Girl:  “No, he’s allright.”
4.  Bobtalk:  T9-4:02 “Something smells good, what is that?”
5.  Female intruder on stage at T17-4:24 (during Rolling Stone) “with no direction home”
6.  T17-5:02:  Bob wishes everyone “Happy Mothers’ Day, happy Fathers’ Day too!”

Bob on keyboards (electric piano?) for It Ain’t Me Babe.

Nice performance, Bob’s having a great time — what happened only a month later?

